

# Muhammad Usman Farooq

Frontend Web Developer

♥ 306 Street 16 G-15/4 Islamabad, Pakistan, 44000 Islamabad

## Summary

I am a front-end web developer for the last year. My expertise shine when it comes to javascript, CSS, and HTML 5. I can build the site using simple HTML 5, CSS, and complex websites by using React Js. I can also develop a website using some of the most famous platforms i.e WordPress, Wix, and Square space.

#### Education

Matric 2014 - 2016

O.P.F Boys College, Islamabad

F.S.C (Pre-Engineering) 2016 - 2018

Punjab Colloege, Blue Area, Islamabad

Bachelor's in Computer Science 2018 - 2022

Shaheed Zulfikar Ali Bhutto Institute of Science and Technology,

Islamabad

Current CGPA: 3.1

## Internships

Front-end Developer Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

Securities and Exchange Commission of Pakistan, Islamabad

## **Work Experience**

Content Writer 2017 - Present

Freelancer

Graphic Desginer 2019 - Present

Freelancer

Frond-end Developer 2021 - Present

Freelancer

#### Personal details

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/usman-farooq-61ba08197

Fiverr

fiverr.com/theedgewriter

Upwork

upwork.com/freelancers/~01 05c9a98d08a00b82

#### Skills

**Developing Web Appliction** 

Landing Page for Personal Website

Game Development

Team leading & Building